<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kdeconnect.kcm.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Connect</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connectxx</name>
  <summary>Seamless connection of your devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Naadloze verbinding met uw apparaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ligação transparente aos seus dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sömlös anslutning av dina apparater</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Безшовне з’єднання для усіх ваших пристроїв</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSeamless connection of your devicesxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer:

        

        Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Connect biedt verschillende functies om uw telefoon en uw computer: merk op dat het nodig is om KDE Connect op uw computer te installeren om deze app te laten werken en de bureabladversie up-to-date te houden met de Android-versie om de laatste functies te laten werken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Connect oferece diversas funcionalidades para integrar o seu telefone com o seu computador: Lembre-se por favor que terá de instalar o KDE Connect com o seu computador para esta aplicação funcionar e deverá manter a versão no ambiente de trabalho actualizada com a versão para Android, para que as últimas funcionalidades funcionem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-anslut tillhandahåller flera funktioner för att integrera telefon och dator. Observera att KDE-anslut måste installeras på datorn för att appen ska fungera, och att skrivbordsdatorns version måste hållas uppdaterad tillsammans med Androidversionen för att de senaste funktionerna ska fungera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У KDE Connect передбачено декілька можливостей для інтеграції вашого телефону з вашим комп’ютером. Будь ласка, зауважте, що вам доведеться встановити KDE Connect на ваш комп’ютер, щоб скористатися цією програмою, а також підтримувати актуальність версії на комп’ютері та версії для Android, щоб мати змогу скористатися найсвіжішими можливостями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Connect provides several features to integrate your phone and your computer: Please note you will need to install KDE Connect on your computer for this app to work, and keep the desktop version up-to-date with the Android version for the latest features to work.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://community.kde.org/KDEConnect/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdeconnect</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/index.php?application=kdeconnect-kde&amp;language=en</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/plasmoid.png</image>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/kcm.png</image>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdeconnect/gnome3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdeconnectd</binary>
    <binary>kdeconnect-cli</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
